Guide to the Central Washington University Athletics Department, Team Sports Collection 1923-2007 (bulk 1965-1995)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Scrapbooks, XI
  - Volleyball Team, Seniors, Alumni Photographs, 2006-2017 (Box-folder 165-5)
  - Softball Team, ALS Game, Seniors Photographs, 2004-2010 (Box-folder 165-6)
  - Women's Soccer Team, Alumni, Seniors Photographs, 2007-2013 (Box-folder 165-7)
  - Women's Basketball Team, Hoopin' It Up In Alaska Signed Tee Shirt, 2008- (Box-folder 165-8)
  - Volleyball Team, GNAC Championships Tee Shirt, 2004- (Box-folder 165-9)
  - Football Team, Posters, 2008-2011 (Box-folder 165-10)
  - Volleyball Team, Poster, 2019- (Box-folder 165-11)
  - Men's Basketball, Northwest Nazarene vs. Central Washington University, 6/26/1905- (Box-folder 166-1)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington vs. South Indiana 12/9/1999 (Box-folder 166-2)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. NNC, 12/30/1999- (Box-folder 166-3)
  - Men's Basketball, Scrimmage, 10/28/2000- (Box-folder 166-4)
  - Men's Basketball, MBO UAA vs. CWU, N/A- (Box-folder 166-5)
  - Men's Basketball, Championship Game Central Washington University vs. Fayetteville State, 11/18/2000- (Box-folder 166-6)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. UPS, 12/30/2000- (Box-folder 166-7)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Bemidji State, 12/2/2000- (Box-folder 166-8)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington Universityl vs. Humbolt State, 2/10/2001- (Box-folder 166-9)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Alaska Fairbanks, 1/4/2001- (Box-folder 166-10)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Henderson State, 12/16/2000- (Box-folder 166-11)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington Universityl vs. Blue Angels, 12/29/2000- (Box-folder 166-12)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Northwest Nazarene, 2/22/2001- (Box-folder 166-13)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Central Missouri, 12/15/2000- (Box-folder 166-14)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU at WSU, 1/11/2001- (Box-folder 166-15)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs Alaska Anchorage, 1/6/2001- (Box-folder 166-16)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Seattle Pacific, 1/8/2001- (Box-folder 166-17)
  - Men's Basketball, MSU-Billings vs. CWU, 2/3/2001- (Box-folder 166-18)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Angelo State, 12/1/2000- (Box-folder 166-19)
  - Men's Basketball, Saint Martins vs. Central Washington, 11/28/2000- (Box-folder 166-20)
  - Men's Basketball, Slam Dunk Contest, 11/8/2006- (Box-folder 166-21)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. SMC, 2/21/1998- (Box-folder 166-22)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Western Oregon, 12/2/1999- (Box-folder 166-23)
  - Men's Basketball, WWU vs. CWU, 2000-01- (Box-folder 166-24)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Seattle, 2/24/2001- (Box-folder 166-25)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Washington, 11/12/2002- (Box-folder 166-26)
  - Men's Basketball, Seattle Pacific vs. Central Washington University, 3/8/2003- (Box-folder 166-27)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Humbolt State, 3/4/2003- (Box-folder 166-28)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University, 12/8/2001- (Box-folder 166-29)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon University, 2/8/2001- (Box-folder 166-30)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs Chico State, 11/24/2001- (Box-folder 166-31)
  - Men's Basketball, WNMU vs. CWU, 2/1/2001- (Box-folder 166-32)
  - Men's Basketball, Virginia Union vs. CWU, 11/17/2000- (Box-folder 166-33)
  - Men's Basketball, Regional Tournament - Seattle Pacific vs. Central Washington University, 3/8/2001- (Box-folder 166-34)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Seattle University, 1/25/2001- (Box-folder 166-35)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. NNU, 1/27/2001- (Box-folder 166-36)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU v. CSU Bakersfield, 12/19/2004- (Box-folder 166-37)
  - Men's Basketball, BYUH vs. CWU, 1/16/1997- (Box-folder 166-38)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University @ Chico State University, 11/29/2003- (Box-folder 166-39)
  - Men's Basketball, WOU vs. CWU, 12/4/2003- (Box-folder 166-40)
  - Men's Basketball, Scrimmage, 11/4/2000- (Box-folder 166-41)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University @ Western Oregon University, 1/13/2001- (Box-folder 166-42)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Seattle Pacific University, 2/17/2001- (Box-folder 166-43)
  - Scrimmage, 10/21/2000- (Box-folder 166-44)
  - Central Washington University vs. Saint Martin's University, 3/2/2001- (Box-folder 166-45)
  - CWU vs. MSUB, 12/1/2006- (Box-folder 166-46)
  - Central Washington University at Seattle University, 12/14/1999- (Box-folder 166-47)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU Alumni Classic, 6/22/1905- (Box-folder 166-48)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Fort Lewis, 12/29/1999- (Box-folder 166-49)
  - CWSC vs. EWSC, 10/20/1973- (Box-folder 167-1)
  - Football, red roll (Box-folder 167-2)
  - CWSC vs. Simon Fraser, 10/9/1976- (Box-folder 167-3)
  - CWU vs. Linfield, 1989- (Box-folder 167-4)
  - CWSC vs. OIT, 10/5/1974- (Box-folder 167-5)
  - Central Washington vs. Pacific Lutheran, 10/6/1984- (Box-folder 167-6)
  - Football, CWU vs. EWU, 9/8/1984- (Box-folder 167-7)
  - CWU vs. PLU, 10/4/1980- (Box-folder 167-8)
  - Central Washington University vs. Oregon College of ED., 11/15/1980- (Box-folder 167-9)
  - Central Washington University vs. Simon Frasier, 11/3/1984- (Box-folder 167-10)
  - CWSC vs. PLU, Oct-64- (Box-folder 167-11)
  - CWSC vs. EWSC, 10/20/1973- (Box-folder 167-12)
  - CWU vs. Whitworth, 9/26/1987- (Box-folder 167-13)
  - CWSC vs. OIT, 10/27/1973- (Box-folder 167-14)
  - CWU vs. SFU, 11/12/1988- (Box-folder 167-15)
  - Football, CWU VS. EWU, 9/8/1984- (Box-folder 167-16)
  - Football, CWU VS. EWU, 9/8/1984- (Box-folder 167-17)
  - Football, CWU VS. Lewis and Clark, 9/29/1984- (Box-folder 167-18)
  - CWU vs. Oregon Tech, 10/20/1984- (Box-folder 167-19)
  - Central Washington University vs. Lewis and Clark, 10/18/1986- (Box-folder 167-20)
  - Men's Basketball, Controlled Scrimmage (Box-folder 168-1)
  - Men's Basketball, SPU vs. CWU, 1999-2000- (Box-folder 168-2)
  - Men's Basketball, Central vs. Coker, 12/29/2001- (Box-folder 168-3)
  - Men's Basketball, Central vs. Anchorage, 1/5/2002- (Box-folder 168-4)
  - Men's Basketball, Central vs. Seattle Pacific, 2/17/2001- (Box-folder 168-5)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Morningside, 12/18/1999- (Box-folder 168-6)
  - Men's Basketball, Central @ Western WA., 1/31/2002- (Box-folder 168-7)
  - Men's Basketball, Central vs. St. Martin's College, 1/26/2002- (Box-folder 168-8)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Western Oregon Univ., 2/21/2002- (Box-folder 168-9)
  - Men's Basketball, Central vs. SPU (Box-folder 168-10)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Ship U., 11/19/1999- (Box-folder 168-11)
  - Mens's Basketball, Saint Martins vs. Central Washington University, 12/21/1999- (Box-folder 168-12)
  - Men's Basketball, Seattle U. vs. CWU, 2/12/2000- (Box-folder 168-13)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Seattle Pacific, 3/11/2000- (Box-folder 168-14)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Cal-State San Bernadino, 3/10/2000- (Box-folder 168-15)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. MSUB, 1/27/2000- (Box-folder 168-16)
  - Men's Basketball, Central vs. UAF, 1/20/2000- (Box-folder 168-17)
  - Mens's Basketball, CWU vs. WNMU, 1/29/2000- (Box-folder 168-18)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. WWU, 2/26/2000- (Box-folder 168-19)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. SPU, 2/19/2000- (Box-folder 168-20)
  - Men's Basketball, WOU vs. CWU, 2/3/2000- (Box-folder 168-21)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. St. Martins, 1/15/2000- (Box-folder 168-22)
  - Men's Basketball, HSU vs. CWU, 2/5/2000- (Box-folder 168-23)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU @ SCU, 1/6/2000- (Box-folder 168-24)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. WWU, 1/8/2000- (Box-folder 168-25)
  - Men's Basketball, Saint Martins vs. Central Washington, 2/17/2000- (Box-folder 168-26)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. BYU Hawaii, 3/3/2000- (Box-folder 168-27)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington vs. Seattle Pacific, 2/2/2002- (Box-folder 168-28)
  - Men's Basketball, Central vs. Northwest Nazarene, 1/10/2002- (Box-folder 168-29)
  - Men's Basketball, Western State vs. Central @ Westminister, 11/29/2002- (Box-folder 168-30)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington vs. Western Oregon University, 1/19/2002- (Box-folder 168-31)
  - Men's Basketball, CSUB vs. Central Washington, 12/28/2002- (Box-folder 168-32)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington vs. Seattle University, 2/14/2002- (Box-folder 168-33)
  - Men's Basketball, Sons Blue Angels vs. Central Washington, 11/16/2002- (Box-folder 168-34)
  - Men's Basketball, Central vs. NNC, 11/22/2002- (Box-folder 168-35)
  - Men's Basketball, Northwest Nazarene vs. Central Washingotn, 2/20/2003- (Box-folder 168-36)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington @ Seattle University, 1/23/2003- (Box-folder 168-37)
  - Men's Basketball, Saint Martins vs. Central Washington, 2/27/2003- (Box-folder 168-38)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Blue Angels @ UW, 11/12/2002- (Box-folder 168-39)
  - Men's Basketball, Alaska Anchorage vs. Central Washington, 2/6/2003- (Box-folder 168-40)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington vs. HSU, 2/13/2003- (Box-folder 168-41)
  - Men's Basketball, UAF vs. CWU, 1/3/2002- (Box-folder 168-42)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU @ WOU, 2/15/2003- (Box-folder 168-43)
  - end of Seattle U beg. Of NNU, 1/10/2004- (Box-folder 169-1)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. NWN (Box-folder 169-2)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Warner Pacific (Box-folder 169-3)
  - Men's Basketball, WWU @ CWU, 2/4/2006- (Box-folder 169-4)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. WWU, 2/1/2007- (Box-folder 169-5)
  - Men's Basketball, HSU @ CWU, 1/22/2005- (Box-folder 169-6)
  - Men's Basketball, WWU @ CWU, 1/8/2005- (Box-folder 169-7)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. GCU (Box-folder 169-8)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Bakersfield, 12/8/2004- (Box-folder 169-9)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. WWU (Box-folder 169-10)
  - Men's Basketball, NNU @ CWU, 1/21/2006- (Box-folder 169-11)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Central Arkansas, 17-Dec- (Box-folder 169-12)
  - Men's Basketball, NDNU vs. CWU (Box-folder 169-13)
  - Men's Basketball, St. Martins vs. CWU, 2/11/2006- (Box-folder 169-14)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Chico St., 11/15/2005- (Box-folder 169-15)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Blue Angels (Box-folder 169-16)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. WOU, 2/5/2005- (Box-folder 169-17)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Australia - 2nd Half, 11/17/2004- (Box-folder 169-18)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Warner Pacific - 2nd Half, 11/20/2004- (Box-folder 169-19)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington vs. Saint Martin's, 2/7/2008- (Box-folder 169-20)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. CAV - Central Arkansas, 17-Dec- (Box-folder 169-21)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Edmonds CC (scrimmage), 6/25/1905- (Box-folder 169-22)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. NNU, 3/3/2007- (Box-folder 169-23)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Alaska, 1/4/2007- (Box-folder 169-24)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. UAA, 1/6/2007- (Box-folder 169-25)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Montana Tech, 11/24/2007- (Box-folder 169-26)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Cal State Bakersfield, 12/19/2004- (Box-folder 169-27)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Alaska Fairbanks, 1/29/2004- (Box-folder 169-28)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. HSU, 1/26/2006- (Box-folder 169-29)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington vs. Saint Martin's, 1/12/2006- (Box-folder 169-30)
  - Men's Basketball, Central at Grand Canyon Game #2 (Box-folder 169-31)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Alderson Brondds (Box-folder 169-32)
  - Men's Basketball, Stanislaus vs. Central Washington University (Box-folder 169-33)
  - Men's Basketball, WSU vs. CWU, 11/5/2006- (Box-folder 169-34)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Saint Leo, 11/25/2003- (Box-folder 169-35)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. North Dakota, 12/30/2006- (Box-folder 169-36)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University @ Humboldt State, 12/6/2003- (Box-folder 169-37)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University @ NNU, 2/16/2006- (Box-folder 169-38)
  - Men's Basketball, MSUB vs CWU, 12/1/2006- (Box-folder 169-39)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU @ WOU, 1/28/2006- (Box-folder 169-40)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washinton University vs. Colorado School of Mins @ Chico, 11/28/2003- (Box-folder 169-41)
  - Men's Basketball, Seattle University vs. Central Washington University, 1/27/2005- (Box-folder 169-42)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University @ NW Nazarene, 1/29/2005- (Box-folder 169-43)
  - Men's Basketball, Saint Martin's vs. Central Washington University, 2/27/2004- (Box-folder 169-44)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Northwest Nazarene, 1/10/2004- (Box-folder 169-45)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Cal State LA, 12/30/2004- (Box-folder 169-46)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Western Washington University, 2/19/2004- (Box-folder 169-47)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. WWU, 1/17/2004- (Box-folder 169-48)
  - Men's Basketball, Seattle University vs. Central Washington University, 2/7/2004- (Box-folder 169-49)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. Hutchinson (Box-folder 169-50)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. University of Min. Crookston, 11/21/2003- (Box-folder 169-51)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. NW Missouri in Las Vegas, 12/19/2003- (Box-folder 169-52)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Calfornia Baptist (Box-folder 169-53)
  - Men's Basketball, HSU @ CWU, 1/22/2005- (Box-folder 169-54)
  - Men's Basketball, UAF vs. CWU, 1/15/2005- (Box-folder 169-55)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University at Saint Martin's University, 12/4/2004- (Box-folder 169-56)
  - Men's Basketball, SPU vs. CWU, 3/10/2006- (Box-folder 169-57)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Chico State, 11/26/2004- (Box-folder 169-58)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Cal State Bakersfield, 18-Dec- (Box-folder 169-59)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Florida Southern, 12/29/2003- (Box-folder 169-60)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Seattle, 1/8/2004- (Box-folder 169-61)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU vs. CSULA, 12/30/2004- (Box-folder 169-62)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Nebraska - Omaha at Las Vegas, 12/20/2003- (Box-folder 169-63)
  - Men's Basketball, SMC vs. Central Washington University, 2/1/2003- (Box-folder 169-64)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Western Baptist, 12/30/2003- (Box-folder 169-65)
  - Men's Basketball, Central Washington University vs. Seattle Pacific University, 2/21/2004- (Box-folder 169-66)
  - Men's Basketball, CWU @ WOU, 2/19/2005- (Box-folder 169-67)
  - 3 Unlabeled (Box-folder 170-)
  - O.C.E vs. CWSC Offense, 11/3/1973- (Box-folder 170-1)
  - Scrimmage, 9/10/1988- (Box-folder 170-2)
  - CWU vs. EWW, 9/8/1984- (Box-folder 170-3)
  - CWU vs. Southern Oregon, 11/3/1979- (Box-folder 170-4)
  - CWU vs. WWU, 10/27/1979- (Box-folder 170-5)
  - CWU vs. Simon Fraser, 9/21/1980- (Box-folder 170-6)
  - CWU vs. Oregon Tech, 10/20/1984- (Box-folder 170-7)
  - Central Washington University vs. Eastern Oregon University, 9/15/1984- (Box-folder 170-8)
  - CWU vs. Whitworth, 9/27/1986- (Box-folder 170-9)
  - CWSC vs. Whitworth, 10/8/1966- (Box-folder 170-10)
  - CWSC vs. OCS, 11/13/1976- (Box-folder 170-11)
  - Football, Central Washington University vs. Western Oregon University, 10/17/1981- (Box-folder 170-12)
  - Central Washington University vs. Whitworth, 9/22/1984- (Box-folder 170-13)
  - CWU vs. UPS, 11/2/1985- (Box-folder 170-14)
  - CWSC vs. Eastern Oregon Univeristy, 10/16/1976- (Box-folder 170-15)
  - CWU vs. OIT, 1/17/1987- (Box-folder 170-16)
  - CWSC vs. Lewis and Clark (Defense), 9/22/1973- (Box-folder 170-17)
  - CWSC vs. Lewis and Clark (Offense), 9/22/1973- (Box-folder 170-18)
  - CWSC vs. Lewis and Clark, 9/22/1972- (Box-folder 171-1)
  - CWU vs. UPS, 1984- (Box-folder 171-2)
  - CWU vs. UPS, 1984- (Box-folder 171-3)
  - OCS vs. CWSC, 11/3/1973- (Box-folder 171-4)
  - CWSC vs. San Francisco State, 11/7/1970- (Box-folder 171-5)
  - Central Washington University Vs. Whitworth, 9/22/1980- (Box-folder 171-6)
  - CWSC vs. San Francisco State, 11/7/1970- (Box-folder 171-7)
  - Football, WOS vs. CWU, 11/17/1984- (Box-folder 171-8)
  - Football, WOS vs. CWU, 11/18/1984- (Box-folder 171-9)
  - CWSC vs. Simon Fraser, 11/15/1975- (Box-folder 171-10)
  - Central Washington University vs. University of Puget Sound, 11/1/1986- (Box-folder 171-11)
  - CWSC vs. OTI, 10/7/1972- (Box-folder 171-12)
  - CWSC vs. PLU, 10/20/1965- (Box-folder 171-13)
  - CWSC vs. WWSC, 10/1/1966- (Box-folder 171-14)
  - CWSC vs. EWU, 10/31/1970- (Box-folder 171-15)
  - 2 Unlabled (Box-folder 171-)
  - Scrimmage, 9/1/1982- (Box-folder 171-16)
  - CWSC vs. WWSC, 11/15/1970- (Box-folder 171-17)
  - CWSC vs. Portland St., 10/13/1973- (Box-folder 171-18)
  - Humboldt St. vs CWSC, 1966- (Box-folder 171-19)
  - CWU vs. PLU, 10/4/1980- (Box-folder 172-1)
  - CWSC vs. Whitworth, 10/8/1966- (Box-folder 172-2)
  - CWSC vs. Whitworth, 1965- (Box-folder 172-3)
  - CWSC vs. EWSC, 1965- (Box-folder 172-4)
  - CWSC vs. Western, 11/12/1966- (Box-folder 172-5)
  - 2 Unlabeled (Box-folder 172-)
  - Central Washington University vs. Southern Oregon, 11/8/1986- (Box-folder 172-6)
  - CWSC, 1965- (Box-folder 172-7)
  - Central Washington University vs. Linfield College, 9/20/1986- (Box-folder 172-8)
  - UPS vs. CWSC, 1965- (Box-folder 172-9)
  - HSC vs. CWSC #2, 1965- (Box-folder 172-10)
  - HSC vs. CWSC #3, 1965- (Box-folder 172-11)
  - unlabeled, 1967- (Box-folder 172-)
  - CWU vs. PLU, Oct-87- (Box-folder 172-12)
  - CWSC vs. Portland State, 10/24/1966- (Box-folder 172-13)
  - CWU vs. PLU, Oct-87- (Box-folder 172-14)
  - CWSC vs. WWC, 10/10/1964- (Box-folder 172-15)
  - CWSC vs. WWU (Box-folder 172-16)
  - CWU vs. Lewis and Clark, 9/29/1984- (Box-folder 172-17)
  - All-American, NCAA, and NAIA Track and Field Awards, 1995-2004 (Box-folder 173-1)
  - All Academic NCAA Division II Cross Country Team Awards, 1999-2006 (Box-folder 173-2)
  - Athletics Directors Association and Academic Achievement Awards and GNAC Academic All-Conference Awards, 2014-2017 (Box-folder 173-3)
  - All-American and All-Academic Cross Country and Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2006 (Box-folder 173-4)
  - All-Academic and All-American Cross Country and Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2007-2008 (Box-folder 173-5)
  - All-Academic and All-American Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2009-2010 (Box-folder 173-6)
  - All-Academic and All-American Cross Country and Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2011 (Box-folder 173-7)
  - All-Academic, All-American, and All-Region Cross Country and Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2012-2013 (Box-folder 173-8)
  - All-Academic, All-American, and All-Region Cross Country and Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2014 (Box-folder 173-9)
  - All-Academic, All-American, and All-Region Cross Country and Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2015 (Box-folder 173-10)
  - All-Academic and All-American Cross Country and Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2016 (Box-folder 173-11)
  - All-Academic, All-America, and All-Region Cross Country and Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2017 (Box-folder 173-12)
  - All-Academic, All-America, and All-Region Cross Country and Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2018 (Box-folder 173-13)
  - All-American and All-Academic Track and Field Awards - 2019 (Box-folder 173-14)
  - All-Academic and All-America Track and Field Awards - 2020 (Box-folder 173-15)
  - All-Academic Cross Country and Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2021 (Box-folder 173-16)
  - All-Academic Cross Country and Track and Field Individual and Team Awards - 2022 (Box-folder 173-17)
  - National Association of Intercollegiate Athletics - Cross Country All-Americans and All-America Scholar Athletes, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 173-18)
  - Track and Field Awards - Tyler Fischer and Taylor Fettig, 2009-2016 (Box-folder 173-19)
  - GNAC Championships Programs - Track and Field and Cross Country, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 174-1)
  - GNAC Championships Programs - Track and Field and Cross Country, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 174-2)
  - GNAC Championships Programs - Track and Field and Cross Country, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 174-3)
  - GNAC Championships Programs - Track and Field and Cross Country, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 174-4)
  - GNAC Championships Programs - Track and Field and Cross Country, 2012-2014 (Box-folder 174-5)
  - GNAC Championships Programs - Track and Field and Cross Country, 2016-2018 (Box-folder 174-6)
  - GNAC Championships Programs - Track and Field and Cross Country, 2019-2021 (Box-folder 174-7)
  - GNAC Championships Programs - Track and Field and Cross Country, 2022-2023 (Box-folder 174-8)
  - CWU Track and Field Records, 2001-2008 (Box-folder 174-9)
  - CWU Track and Field Records, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 174-10)
  - CWU Track and Field Records, 2012-2016 (Box-folder 174-11)
  - CWU Track and Field Records, 2017-2019 (Box-folder 174-12)
  - CWU Outdoor Track and Field Records, 2021-2023 (Box-folder 174-13)
  - CWU Cross Country College Female Team of the Year Plaque - Monday Morning Quarterbacks Club, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 175-1)
  - GNAC CWU Men's Cross Country Academic Team Champion Plaque, 2017-2018 (Box-folder 175-2)
  - GNAC CWU Men's Track and Field Academic Team Champion Plaque, 2017-2018 (Box-folder 175-3)
  - GNAC Men's Outdoor Track and Field Champions Plaque, 2007- (Box-folder 175-4)
  - GNAC Men's Indoor Track and Field Champions Plaque, 2007- (Box-folder 175-5)
  - GNAC Men's Outdoor Track and Field Champions Plaque, 2006- (Box-folder 175-6)
  - GNAC CWU Men's Cross Country Academic Team Champion Plaque, 2018-2019 (Box-folder 175-7)
  - GNAC CWU Men's Track and Field Academic Team Champion Plaque, 2021-2022 (Box-folder 175-8)
  - GNAC Women's Cross Country Champions Plaque, 2004- (Box-folder 175-9)
  - GNAC Men's Outdoor Track and Field Champions Plaque, 2007- (Box-folder 175-10)
  - GNAC Men's Indoor Track and Field Champions Plaque, 2007- (Box-folder 175-11)
  - GNAC Men's Outdoor Track and Field Champions Plaque, 2006- (Box-folder 175-12)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor, 2007- (Box-folder 176-1)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Indoor, 2012- (Box-folder 176-2)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor, 2012- (Box-folder 176-3)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Indoor, 2006- (Box-folder 176-4)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor, 2011- (Box-folder 176-5)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Indoor, 2011- (Box-folder 176-6)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - CSU, 2011- (Box-folder 176-7)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Indoor - U of H, 2009- (Box-folder 176-8)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - CSU, 2013- (Box-folder 176-9)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Indoor - Reggie Lewis Track and Athletic Center, 2005- (Box-folder 176-10)